phs.org 2003-06-22

# Presbyterian Healthcare Services - Privacy Policy

 |   
---|---  
  
**Presbyterian Healthcare Services Privacy Policies**

**PHS Health Information (HIPAA) Privacy Policy**

This notice describes how medical information about you may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information (.pdf). 

**Notificación Conjunta Sobre Prácticas De Respeto De La Vida Privada**

Esta notificación describe la manera en que su información médica puede ser utilizada y divulgada, y cómo usted puede tener acceso a dicha información (.pdf). 

**Presbyterian Healthcare Services Website Privacy Policy**

****

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

We collect two kinds of information from visitors to our website: 

  1. We monitor our website **traffic statistics** , including: 
    * where visitor traffic comes from
    * how traffic flows within the website 
    * browser type ****
****

**Traffic statistics** help us improve the website and find out what visitors find interesting and useful.

  2. If you fill out a form on the PHS website, you might provide us with **personal information** such as your name, address, billing information, health plan member status, etc. 

PHS uses your **personal information** to reply to your concerns. We save this information as needed to keep responsible records and handle inquiries. 

We do not sell, trade, or rent our visitors' personal information to other companies or partners.

****

**Security measures**

We use technologies such as Secure Socket Layers (SSL) to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

****

**Our commitment to children's privacy**

Protecting the safety and privacy of children is important to us. We do not collect or ask for information about children on the PHS website. 

The PHS Babynet site maintains temporary information about infants born at Presbyterian hospitals. Only visitors who have been given the security code by the baby's parents will be able to see the new baby. PHS staff will not give out the security code to anyone except the parents. 

****

**Other disclosure of personal information**

PHS will not use or disclose your personal information without your consent except as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities. 

This policy does not apply to information you post in our on-line chat room.

****

**Change your personal information**

To remove your e-mail address from any www.phs.org mailing list, send an e-mail requesting removal to [info@phs.org](mailto:info@phs.org). 

****

**Your consent**

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of the information discussed above by Presbyterian Healthcare Services. We will post changes in this policy on this page as they occur so that you know what information we collect, how we are using it, how it is secured, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

****

**Who collects this information?**

Presbyterian Healthcare Services maintains the PHS website. If you have questions or comments about privacy, contact us at:

P.O. Box 26666  
Albuquerque, NM 87125-6666  
E-mail: [info@phs.org](mailto:info@phs.org)  
Telephone: (505) 923-8612

* * *

Home | About PHS | Health Info | Health Plans | Employment | Facilities | Providers | News | Disclaimer | Site Map | [E-mail](https://secure.phs.org/healthplan/hprequest.htm) | [Search](http://www.phs.org:8765/)

All content on this site is copyrighted by Presbyterian Healthcare Services. No images or content may be reproduced for commercial use or distribution without the written authorization of PHS. 041103
